

Evgenii Tagiltsev

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Phone Number +420603889044

Website https://eugeneslab.net

Email Address tagiltsev.evgenii@gmail.com

LinkedinPersonal page

GitHub Projects

SKILLS

C/C++ Advanced **Qt** Advanced

QML

REST API

Advanced

Advanced

Git

Subverstion

Advanced

Intermediate

MySQL/SQLite
Intermediate

C# (ASP.NET)

Linux

Novice

LIIIUX

Android SDK

administration

Novice

Novice

scss

HTML/CSS/JS
Novice

Novice

Cryptography

Fundamental Awareness

LANGUAGES

Russian

English

Native

B1

Czech

PERSONAL PROFILE

Accomplished software developer with extensive experience of task solving using various programming languages including C++ and C, internet protocols, programming for embedded systems, programming desktop applications with user interfaces, or console applications.

Demonstrated ability to work as a crucial member of a team within the construction department framework of an aviation company. Strong track record of both high-quality assignments, namely producing custom-made devices for customers, in addition to experimental personal projects, such as creating devices controlled by microcontrollers or designing an application for private safe online messaging, currently in progress. Highly interested in current developments in the ICT and different fields of study. Other hobbies include improvement of English on a daily basis, advancement in personal projects, together with playing computer games and cycling

EDUCATION

Ural Federal University, Faculty of Foundation education, Department of Information systems and technologies

(August 2011 -July 2015)

Bachelor's Degree Information Technology

Diploma Thesis: Detecting human movements on video taken from camera

WORK EXPERIENCE

Experimental department of Ural factory of civil aviation

(November 2014 - May 2019)

Engineer - programmer

Responsibilities:

- Developing custom-made programs based on customers' requirements
- Developing algorithms for task solving
- · Testing and debugging
- Developing sample devices and prototypes to check solved tasks
- · Deploying applications to customers' devices
- Supporting, updating, and upgrading applications

Demlabs inc.

Ot programmer

(July 2019 - February 2020)

Responsibilities:

- Developing a GUI application based on prototypes
- Developing a service application for connection with Cellframe Node

Redwood Games

(January 2020 - April 2020)

Qt programmer

Responsibilities:

• Fixing bugs of "Plutocracy" game

CERTIFICATIONS

Avionic of aircraft

Kazan Aircraft University

Document number: 162400319885

ACHIEVEMENTS

Vysočina - the Best Holiday

June 2020

Participant and prizewinner: Competition focused on tourism promotion in the Vysočina Region in the CR - awarded as one among the most creative solutions. Developed Routefinder - an app which enables tourists to filter touristic routes in the region according to their preferences - distance, objects, cities, etc. The app offers a wide selection of routes written in its database from which tourists can choose the route most suitable for them achieved

Project Eurobot

March 2013

Participant and team prizewinner: An international robotic competition - 3rd place achieved.

HOBBIES

Cycling

Computer games

Personal development

Language improvement

Board games